Contact

erika_shor@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/erika-shor-crna-5b79a691 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

ACLS

BLS

Nursing

Languages

English

Certifications

PALS-pediatric advanced life support

VAD-Ventricular Assist Device including HM II and III, Heartware, Centrimag and Thoratec TAH (total artificial heart)

Intra-aortic Balloon Pump (IABP)

<u>BLS-Basic Life Support CPR</u>

Honors-Awards

Dean's List

Erika Shor, CRNA

Nurse Anesthetist at The MetroHealth System (Cleveland, OH) Greater Cleveland

Summary

I'm a new graduate CRNA and earned my MSN from Case Western Reserve University. My nursing background was in a CVICU caring for primarily heart and lung transplant patients along with mechanical circulatory support devices. I also have experience with cardiac surgery patients and as a Flyout RN in organ procurement.

Experience

The MetroHealth System (Cleveland, OH) Nurse Anesthetist January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Case Western Reserve University
Student Registered Nurse Anesthetist
June 2017 - December 2019 (2 years 7 months)
Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

I'm currently studying to be a certified registered nurse anesthetist.

Cleveland Clinic

6 years 2 months

Registered Nurse

May 2016 - July 2018 (2 years 3 months)

Cardiac Surgery Flyout-heart/lung organ procurement

- Assist cardiothoracic surgeons and the first assist in procuring heart and lungs for organ donation.
- Work with organ procurement organizations in facilitating smooth procurements and communicating with the home surgical team.

Registered Nurse

July 2014 - May 2017 (2 years 11 months)

Cardiovascular Surgical Intensive Care Unit

Developing plans of care for critically ill patients. Patient population includes primarily heart and lung transplants, and open heart surgeries such as CABGs and valve repairs. MICU and SICU overflow patients are occasionally cared

for as well. Report acute changes to the provider and appropriate staff. Care involves monitoring patients on hemodynamic drips, mechanical ventilation, PA catheters, arterial lines, CVVHD/dialysis, and temporary/permanent pacemakers. Advanced monitoring of mechanical circulatory support devices such as impella, tandem heart, LVAD, centrimag, and AV/VV ECMO as well patients requiring total artificial hearts and intra-aortic balloon pump therapy.

Clinical Technician
July 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 1 month)
cvicu j64

- -Performs or assists with technical skills including but are not limited to basic patient care, vital signs, weights, pulse oximetry, point of care testing (POCT), EKG, dressing changes, urinary catheter insertions, phlebotomy, application of external monitoring devices, and removal of chest tubes.
- -Reports abnormal findings or changes in status to RN.
- -Assist with admissions, discharges, and transfers.
- -Ensure the unit is stocked and medication/supply room is clear of clutter.
- -Postmortem care.

Patient Care Nursing Assistant June 2012 - July 2013 (1 year 2 months) Cardiovascular Surgical Stepdown Unit J61

- -Under the supervision of an RN performs basic patient care activities.
- -Assist with skills including but not limited to vital signs, accuchecks, weights, intake and output, assisting patients with personal care and activities of daily living and patient transfers/transport.
- -Reports abnormal findings or changes in status to RN.
- -Assist with keeping patient rooms clean and orderly.

Education

Case Western Reserve University MSN, Nurse Anesthetist (2017 - 2019)

Cleveland State University

Nursing-BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2014)

The University of Akron
Pre-nursing, Pre-Nursing Studies · (2010 - 2010)

Lorain County Community College

Pre-nursing, Pre-Nursing Studies · (2009 - 2009)

Marion L. Steele High School Diploma, High School Diploma · (2005 - 2009)